To be continued...
K...Kotetsu...
Are you...
My strength...
Is sapped...
There's nothing...
I can...
I know you can do it, Muichiro.
Now, stand up.
Father...
To be continued...
I remember.
I remember that I used to love helping Father work.
Hang in there, Mother.
Father just went out to get you some herbs, so...
Mother!
She's burning up.
Here, take my blanket.
That should help, right, Mother?
So cold.
Hang on.
Father will be back soon, all right?
No.
That day...
I lost two people who were dear to me.
Both my mother and my father passed away.
I was ten years old, without any parents.
I was ten years old and completely alone.
No, that's not right.
I was eleven when I found myself alone.
Before then, I used to have a twin brother.
An older brother, and his name was Yuichiro.
Kindness does no good for anyone.
If you try to help somebody in need, you'll only get hurt.
That's not true.
Whatever you do to help others has a way of coming back around and helping yourself someday.
That's what father said.
You're regurgitating the words of a man who got himself killed trying to help someone else.
How could you say something so cold?
He died trying to save our mother.
As if a few herbs would have done anything to heal her at that point.
Don't be so stupid.
Don't say such awful things.
If he hadn't gone out in the middle of a storm, maybe we would have only lost our mother that night.
Please stop saying things like that.
That's going too far.
I'm only telling you how it is.
And stop being so noisy.
You might attract boars.
I guess the Mu and Muichiro stands for incompetence.
This conversation is meaningless.
After all, you can't change the past.
Or maybe the Mu and Muichiro stands for meaningless.
He was unsympathetic and spoke harshly.
I feel that, in a way, I acted like him after I had amnesia.
Life with my brother wasn't easy.
If anything, it was stifling.
I was sure he despised me.
And because of that, I couldn't help but think of him as a cold person.
I remember the seasons changed.
And it was spring.
I'll be back.
I'm gonna fetch some water.
You still haven't gotten any?
Hmm.
The first time I saw her, I couldn't believe it.
She was so beautiful.
I thought she was a white birch spirit.
It turns out, this person was the Master's wife, who came to visit us.
Which meant she traveled all the way up the mountain.
But, in the end, my brother just spewed his usual insults and drove Lady Amane away.
Can you believe it?
She says our ancestors were swordsmen.
Apparently, we're descendants of an amazing swordsman who used something called first breathing.
Why should I care?
Wash the rice already.
Hey, let's become swordsmen.
It's hard to believe demons exist and are out there hurting people.
If we can do something to help, we should.
Right?
So let's become swordsmen and save the people who are suffering.
If we do it together...
What makes you think you could ever save anybody?
You can't cook rice on your own and you're gonna be a swordsman and save others?
Give me a break, Muiichiro!
You sound like mother and father spouting that kind of nonsense.
Stop being so optimistic.
Your mind is poisoned.
Just like mother who told us she was fine and then worked until she collapsed.
Like father who got killed trying to find some herbs.
Even after I tried to stop him.
Even after I begged mother to rest over and over.
The only kind of people who can help others are people who were chosen to do so.
Our ancestors may have been swordsmen, but we are just two hopeless orphans.
People like us are useless.
We're only good for one thing.
And that's dying in the street like dogs.
Our parents met the same fate to prove it.
We'll only end up getting used by that woman.
Why do you think she came all the way here?
We're never talking about this again, got it?
Now hurry up and get dinner ready!
After that incident, we stopped speaking to each other.
Except for the one time we fought briefly when my brother hurled water at Lady Amane, who traveled up the mountain to visit us again.
We're never talking to each other.
Then summer came.
It was blisteringly hot.
So my brother and I were always irritable.
It was a hot night.
The cicadas were singing.
I was 14 years old.
Mmm.
Yeah.
It was horrible.
energy nitrogenjack.
Yeah.
мышx.
Eh.
Yeah.
Mm.
Ah, damn it.
Nothing but a couple of brats, huh?
Whatever.
Muichiro!
Brother!
Shut up!
You're too noisy.
You can cry for help, but no one's coming to help a couple of useless lumbermen like yourselves.
Since it doesn't matter whether you exist or not.
After all, your lives are worthless.
At that moment, all I could see was red.
I went into a violent and uncontrollable rage.
One that boiled from the pit of my stomach.
It came to me naturally.
And while I can't remember exactly what happened next, I still hear that roar.
Even now.
I can't believe a sound like that came from my throat.
From my own mouth.
Before I knew it, the demon was on the brink of death.
But apparently, it couldn't die even with its head smashed in.
So it was suffering.
Soon after, the sun began to rise.
And the demon turned to dust and vanished.
But I couldn't care less about that.
All I wanted was to get to Uichiro and tend to his wounds.
But suddenly, my body felt like it was heavier than lead.
It took me what felt like ages.
Just to reach the house right in front of me.
I beg of you.
Please, I beg of you.
Oh, please, I...
Brother.
You're alive.
Please, dear God, Buddha.
Anyone out there who's listening.
I beg of you.
Save him.
Please save my brother.
He doesn't deserve any of this.
My brother isn't like me.
He's kind.
He's a kind-hearted kid.
Through and through.
He says he wants to help others.
But I got in the way of his dream.
It's my fault.
I'm to blame.
So please...
Please don't punish him.
It's my fault.
And only mine.
The truth is...
I've always known...
About his name.
The Muimoichiro...
Stands for...
Infinity.
Mist breathing.
Fourth form.
Shifting flow.
Slash.
Mist breathing.
Fourth form.
Shifting flow.
Slash.
Kotetsu.
Mr. Tokito.
Don't...
Don't worry about me.
Mr. Hagenesuka.
You have to...
Save him.
And the swords.
Right.
Damn swordsmith.
Damn Philistine.
His focus is absurd.
It's practically inhuman.
Even after all I've done to him, he still won't stop honing that damn sword.
Even when I decimated one of his eyes, he maintained his focus sharpening that sword.
Ooh, I know.
What if I tell him I'm going to kill this one?
He managed to escape the water prison pot, but how is that possible?
It shouldn't be.
I was so certain that his death was imminent that he was the furthest thing from my mind.
No, wait a second.
On the other hand, I didn't notice he escaped because I was so focused on dealing with these two.
Yes!
Hmm?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
What's with that mark on his face?
If I recall the information Lord Muzan gave me, the child with the earrings is the one who has the mark on his face, isn't he?
No, no, no.
It matters not.
How are you standing there so nonchalantly?
The attack I landed on you earlier should have left your body completely paralyzed.
And how are you able to summon even greater speed than our last encounter and wound me?
Octopus face hell!
More koki-dok-dok!
Yoo-hoo!
You didn't expect this octopus flesh to be so springy.
Let's see you try and slash this.
He's still honing that sword. Is he a fool? Surely he's not in his right mind.
His madness is sublime! The swordsmith can wait until I've killed off the Hashira.
I'm sure you know this, but I wasn't trying earlier. But this time I'll give it all I've got so I can crush and absorb you!
Mr. Kanamori, you crafted this sword for me. Mr. Kanamori, thank you.
N-n-no! It was nothing! All I did was follow the instructions your first time!
I'm sure you know this, but I wasn't trying earlier.
I'm sure you know this, but I wasn't trying earlier. But this time I'll give it all I've got so I can crush and absorb you!
Mr. Kanamori, you crafted this sword for me. Mr. Kanamori, thank you.
N-no! It was nothing! All I did was follow the instructions your first swordsmith left me!
That's right. It was Mr. Tetsuido who forged my first sword for me, wasn't it? But he's since passed away from heart disease.
Hm! No matter how many times you replace your sword, it won't change a thing.
Ah, it fits like a glove.
I worry about you very much, boy. After all, who could ever understand what it is you're going through?
How you only have time for battle and training. How you're barely getting by and have no breathing room.
How anxious you must be all the time because you can't seem to remember anything.
And how you strive so hard you end up vomiting blood.
Who could ever understand something like that?
Whenever I lay eyes on the battered swords you've used, it brings a tear to my eye.
Muichiro, listen to me carefully. I feel I won't be around much longer. But I'll still worry about you, even in the afterlife.
Mr. Tetsuido, I'm sorry. I know I made you worry, but I'm alright now. So, rest easy.
Misbreathing. Fifth fork. Sea of clouds and haze!
Your rapid fire chopping had me worried, but it seems like you're not able to keep up with my vase's speed after all.
Are you sure?
What?
Maybe it's because you've lived for hundreds of years, but your senses have grown weary.
I'm going to behead you. I've got much more important things to do than playing with that silly vase of yours.
Don't underestimate me, you damn brat.
Muichiro.
Sorry I couldn't be more gentle with you.
It's just, I could never afford to be that way.
Being compassionate towards others is one more thing that only the chosen can do.
But remember, Muichiro, no matter how virtuous a life you may lead, neither the gods nor Buddha will be the ones to protect you in the end.
That's why I threw myself in front of you that day.
Muichiro, you and I are nothing alike.
Because for the sake of someone else, you can exert infinite strength.
You are one of the chosen ones.
Chosen Ones.
Oh yeah!
Happy birthday, Ms. Konroji.
Let's start with your friends from the village.
Our gifts and all-you-can-eat spread!
All-you-can-eat means I can have as many helpings as I want, right?
Huh?
You're gonna have seconds of all this?
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh!
Now it's time for a Taisho-era secret.
Nowadays, Ms. Konroji's favorite foods are pork cutlets and omelet rice, which are both Western-style foods.
So as a surprise, Nezuko and I got her some for her birthday!
Thank you!
Can I eat them now?
Of course!
Up next, Episode 9, Ms. Tashira, Muichiro Tokito.
Seconds, please!
Already?
Come on, keep them coming!